National Council for the Traditional Arts (NCTA) collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Performer and Genre Lists
  - Genres
Shahla Nikfal and Bahram Sadeghian
Shannon, Joe
Shape Note Singers from National Folk Festival
Shape Note Singing Group
Sharq Arabic Music Ensemble
Shashidhar, Naga
Shashmaqam
Shay, Dick
Sheehy, Dan
Sheehy, Molly
Sheets, Randy
Shelley, Sarah
Shelor, Sammy
Shenandoah Fiddle Style
Shenk, Stu
Shines, Johnny
Shingus, Curtis
Shir Delite
Shirley Caesar & the Caesar Singers
Shoenberg, Eric (Rick)
Short, Lois
Shourds, Harry V.
Si Thoai
Sicilia Antica
Sidiki Conde
Sidle, Kenny
Sills, Lee
Silva, Joao and Manuel Inacio da Silva
Silver Leaf Gospel Singers
Silvertones, The
Simien, Terrance and the Mallet Playboys
Simon and Daniel St. Pierre
Simpkins, Rickie
Sims, Howard "Sandman"
Sinclair Brothers
Singers and Songs Workshop
Singing the Blues
Singing Traditions
Sippie Wallace and Mary Smith McClain
Sissoko, Yacouba
Sissy Kaio And Family
Sissy Kari and Family
Sizemore, Herschel
Skaggs, Ricky and Kentucky Thunder
Skandia Pioneer Trio
Skatalites
Skiamberg, Lorin
Slate Mountain Ramblers
Slide Guitar Traditions
Slim, Memphis
Slobodkin, Nathan
Slovenian Polka Pals
Sluys, Nancy
Slyde, Jimmy
Small, Drink
Smigen-Rothkopf, Lily
Smith Brothers, The
Smith, Bill
Smith, Dennis
Smith, Jackie
Smith, Jesse
Smith, Kenny
Smith, Mike
Smith, Robert
Smith, Whit
Smith, Willie Mae Ford
Smith-Barney, Deborah
Smokey Valley Boys
Snow, Kilby
Snuffy Jenkins & Pappy Sherrill
Snuffy Jenkins and Pappy Sherrill
Soback, Jamie
Sobeck, Jamie Brown
Sockabasin, Blanche
Sokal Tears for Cleveland
Sol Y Canto
Solás
Solás
Solas & Irish Step Dancers
Solecki, Kevin
Solek, Walt
Solo Dance Demonstrations
Solo Religious Music
Solomon Branch Band
Son de Borínquen
Sonny Burgess & the Legendary Pacers
Sons of Hawaii
Sons Of The Whiskey Rebellion, The
Sophia Bilides Trio
Southern Pride
Southern Rail
Southern Scratch
Southern Tradition Bluegrass Band
Southern, Hugh
Sparkman, Steve
Spelman, Akta (the 'genuine fiddlers')
Spellman, Jimmy
Spencer Family
Spencer, Dolly
Spencer, Emily
Spencer, Kilby
Spicer, Robert
Spiritual Highlights
Spitzer, Nick
Spottswood, Dick
Springfield Exit
Sproat, Clyde "Kindy"
Sproat, Clyde and Karin & Gary Haleamau
Sproat, Kindy and Haleamau, Gary
Sproat, Kindy w/Haleamau `Ohana
Sproule, Daithi
Square Dance Federation
Squire, Paul
Sredzienski, Gary
St. James Adult Choir
St. Louis Trio
St. Pierre, Simon
St. Pierre, Simon and Joe Pomerleau
Stafford, Chris
Stafford, Tim
Stanky & The Coal Miners 1995 NFF
Stanley, Ralph
Stanley, Ralph and the Clinch Mountain Boys
Staple Singers 1997
Staples, Mavis
Stars of Hope
Starving On The Family Farm
Steadman, Connie
Steel Unlimited
Steele - McConnell
Steele, Lily
Steffey, Adam
Stephens, James "Guitar Slim"
Stephenson, Joe and Donna
Steve Meisner Band, The
Steve Riley & The Mamou Playboys
Steve Riley and David Greely
Steven Greenman & the Moldavish
Stevens, Harry
Stevie Barr, Chris Harris, Wayne Henderson, Herb K
Stewart, John
Stewart, Ron
Stinson, Kenny Bill
Stoeckl, Nroni
Stomach Steinway
Stone, Bob
Stoneman Family
Stony Point Quartet
Stovall, Babe
Stover, Don
Strachwitz, Chris
Strange Creek Singers
Straw, Sid
Streetsboro Quilting Guild
Strickland, Spencer
String Band Evolution Workshop
String Wizards Workshop
Stringband Music and Dance from the North Carolina
Stringed Instruments of the World
Stubbert, Brenda
Stubbs, Edward L.
Stundza, Jonas
Sturdivant, Lillie D.
Sturgill, Kate
Styles, John
Stylos, Dr. Louis
Sue Richards and Brendan Mulvihill
Sun Rhythm Section
Sunday Gospel Show
Sunshine Skiffle Band
Susan Watts & the Fabulous Spheikehs
Susan, Sylvia and Their Friends
Susso, Papa
Sutphin, Kirk
Sweet Honey In The Rock
Sweezy, Nancy
Swing Low Sweet Chariot
Sykes, Roosevelt
Synar, Mike - US Congressman
T&T Baltimore Steel Band
Ta Pethia
Ta Pethia NFF 49th
Tafoya, Margaret
Takoma Mandoleers
Tales from Rugby
Talkin' The Blues
Talking Duck
Tamara Voslkaya & Anatoly Trofimov
Tamburitzan Workshop
Tang Liangxing And Daughters
Tanner, Henry
Tate, David
Sarbinska, Tatiana
Tavares Brothers
Tavares, Norberto
Taylor, James Alex
Taylor, James Alex & Taylor, Barry
Taylor, Katy
Taylor, Koko
Teater, Visafton och Bal cast
Ted Kolowicz and the Sparks of Fire Orchestra
Ted Lundy, Bob Paisley and the Southern Mountain Boys
Tennessee People (participants in workshop with this title)
Terkel, Studs
Terkishev, Emill
Texas Cowboys, The
The Next Generation
The Squeezebox
Theriaults, The
Thibodeaux, Ambrose
Thomas and Pauline Burt
Thomas, James "Son"
Thomas, Rob
Thomason, Dovie
Thompson, Dorothy
Thompson, Hayden
Thompson, Joe and Odell with John Dee and Janice H
Thornton Spencer and the White Top Mountain Band
Three Generations
Thu Hàng
Thunberg, Ivan and Herman Roberts, Sr.
Thúy Vân
Ti Coca et Wanga Négés
Tibetan Monks from the Drepung Loseling Monastery
Tickell, Kathryn
Tidewater Grass
Tigua Indians
Tim and Mollie O'Brien
Time Jumpers, The
Tinwhistle Workshop
Tito Matos & Juan Gutiérrez
Tito Puente Latin Jazz Ensemble
Tiulana, Paul
Toast String Stretchers
Tobin, Rosemary
Tolino
Tolliver, Speedy
Tony Acosta y sus Tipicos 1993 LFF
Tony Ballog & the Golden Orchestra
Tony Ballog and Gyorgy Batyi
Tony Ballog and His Gypsy Orchestra
Ellis, Tony
Tony Ellis & Friends LFF 1998
Tony Ellis and Friends
Tony Sohns-Bug Zoo
Tony Sohns-Bugs, amphibians, reptiles
Tony Sohns-Creatures of the Wild Worlds
Tony Sohns-Leapin' Lizzards
Top Notches from Kansas City
Torres, Eileen
Torsky, Mary
Toth, Nicholas
Townsend, Graham
Townsend, Henry
Townsend, Henry (NFF 1972)
Henry and Vernell Townsend
Tracie, Gordon Ekvall
Traditional Flutes
Traditional Harmonies Workshop
Traditional Recitations
Trambitas, Gheorghe
Treme Brass Band
Trian
Trice, Willie
Trinidad and Tobago Baltimore Steel Drum Band
Trinidad and Tobago Steelband, The
Trio Chalchihuecan
Trio from REACH
Trio San Antonio
Trofimov, Anatolily
Troupe Languichatte (Haitian Dance Group)
Trowbridge, Ken
Troy MacGillivray, Allan Dewar, Doug Lamey
Troy, Leroy
Trumpold, Dorothy
Tsimouris, Nikitas
Tsoodle, Fred
Tucker, Lois
Tulach Ard Scottish Pipe Band
Tulla Céilí Band
Turas
Turn Your Radio On
Turner, Nap
Turner, Othar and the Rising Star Fife & Drum Band
Turner, Rory
Turtle Mountain Mitchif Perfomers
Tyulyush, Radik
Uallacháin, Pádragín Ní
Underhill, Maureen
Ung, Loung
Ungar, Jay
Ungar, Jay and Lyn Hardy
Union Light Singers
United States Marine Corps Color Guard
Unusual String Things
Upland South and Heartland Fiddlers
Vachon, Josee 1993 LFF
Valahia with Gheorghe Trimbitas
Vallely, Niall
Valley Ramblers, The
Van Arsdale, Paul
Van Arsdale, Paul and Ron West
Van Cleave, Jimmy
Vanaver, Bill
Vanaver, Bill and Livia Drapkin
Vappie, Don
Vaughn Eller and Lawrence Eller
Veltones
Venuti
Vergie Kelly, Horace Boyer, David Marshall Jackson
Veseli Tamburitzans
Vicente Montoya and Margarito Olivas
Viento de Agua
Vigil, Cleofes
Villamil, Felipe Garcia
Vin Bruce and the Acadians
Vinagre, Ana
Vinny Calderone & Angelo Boncore
Vinson, Mose
Vinson, Mose and Mrs. Van Hunt
Violet De Cristoforo
Virgie Kelly, Horace Boyer, David Marshall Jackson
Virginia Banjo Styles (NFF 1977)
Virginia Fiddle Forum
Virginian Indian Intertribal Dance Group & Drum
Vishten
Vlach, John
Vocal Apprenticeships w/Lay & Whitesell, Cephas & Pessar, Cage & Crawford
Volkgert, Redd
Volskaya Russian Trio
Volskaya, Tamara
Vornbrach, Betty
Vuorenmaa, Irene
W.C. Clark
Wabanaki Dance and Drumming
Wacongo Dance Company
Wade and Julia Mainer
Wade Mainer, the Morris Brothers and Steve Ledford
Wade, Stephen
Wagner, Bodie
Wagner, Jim
Walden, Charlie
Walden, Charlie and Pat
Walker, Albertina
Walker, Laura
Walker, Steve
Wall, Eamonn
Wallace, Andy
Wallace, Sippie
Wallin, Cas and Evelyn Ramsey
Wallin, Douglas
Wally McRae and Mac Parker
Walser, Don
Walter Mouton and the Scott Playboys
Walters, Sandy
Wampanoag Native Dancers and Singers
Wanda Jackson & the Lustre Kings
Wareham, Baxter
Warner Williams & Jay Summerour
Washburn, Newton
Washington, Jerry
Wasson, Rickie
Watson, Dale
Watson, Doc
Watson, Peco
Watson, Richard
Watts, Susan
Wawali Bonane & Yoka Nzenze
Wayne Gorbea & Salsa Picante
Wayne Henderson & Jeff Little & Friends
Wayne Henderson & Randy Greer
Wayne Henderson and Friends
Henderson, Wayne
Wayne Toups and Zydecajun
Wedding Traditions Workshop NFF 1992
Wei, Yang
Wells, Gussie
West, Speedy and the Oklahoma Swing Band
Westerman, Floyd
Whelan, Johnny
Whisnant, David
Whistles, Flutes and Harps
Whit Sizemore and the Shady Mountain Ramblers
White Top Mountain Band
White, Buck and the Down Home Folks
White, Johnny
White, Richard
White, Uncle Jessie
Whites, The
Whitstein Brothers, The
Whoopin Hollar Stringband
Why We Held To Our Culture
Wider Horizons
Wiggins, Phil
Wilcox, Jeep
Wild and Wooly West Workshop
Wild Style 25th Anniversary Reunion
Wilkins, Reverend Robert
Will Keys Band
Willams, Nathan
Williams, Arbie
Williams, Bill
Williams, Chris
Williams, Claude
Williams, Horace "Spoons"
Williams, James
Williams, Moses
Williams, Otis
Williams, Steve
Williams, Warner
Williamsburg Fife & Drum Corp
Willie King & the Liberators
Willum Garvey And Robbie O'Connell
Wilson, Chesley Goseyun
Wilson, Edith and Little Brother Montgomery
Wilson, George
Wilson, Joe
Wilson, Joseph
Wilson, Josephine Sutherland
Wilson, Pat
Winch, Terry
Wind Instrument Traditions
Windbags & Blowhards
Winds And Reeds
Wine, Melvin
Winifred Hodges Dancers
Winifred Horan and Friends
Winishut, Donnie and Percy
Wisconsin Lumberjacks
Wolfe Brothers
Womack, Dan
Women And Music Talk And Song
Women In Music
Women In Song
Women's Solo Dance Style
Wong, James Ká Upena
Woo Chin Lion Dance Troupe
Wood, Richard
Woodcock, Donny
Woodcock, Howard
Words, Words, Words
Workman, Nimrod
Workshop Polish Dancers
World Strings Workshop
Wright Kids
Wright Sisters, The
Wright, Earl
Wright, John
Wright, John and Catherine Perrier
Wrigley Sisters
Wylie and the Wild West
Xiang, Betty
Yang Wei & Betty Xiang
Yang, Fang Nhu
Yangqin Zhao-yangin
Yao, Ann
Yaqui Religious Music And Expression Workshop
Yawn, Jesse
YMHA
Yorick's Marionette Theater
Young Peoples' Chorus of Hopewell Baptist Church
Young Stepdancers Showcase
Young, Montana
Yugoslav Dancers from St. Louis
Yugovich Tamburitzans
Yunquin Wang and Friends
Yuqin Wang & Family
Yuqin Wang & Zhengli Xu
Yuqin Wang Dragon Art Studio
Yuri Yunakov Ensemble
Yuri Yunakov Ensemble NFF 1999
Zarzatian, Jack
Zarzyski, Paul
Zay, Harvey
Zed & Samantha Snyder
Zephyr Lightning Bolts
Zespól Harnasie
Zhang, Zhentian
Zivili
Zozimos
Zuttermeister, Emily "Aunty Kau'I"
Zydeco Joe & the Laissez Le Bon Temps Rouler Band
Genres
The following is a list extracted from the "Music Categories" field of the NCTA database. It is provided to show the types of classification that NCTA's events covered - musical styles, dance, crafts, and other arts. Nearly every recording and track has at least one of these terms applied to it. See Access and Restrictions section for more information about the NCTA database.
A Cappella Gospel Music
Acadian
Acadian French music and dance
Accordion - Various Styles
Accordion music
Accordion: Fraco-American
Accordion-Brazilian Forró
Accordion-Cajun
Accordion-Conjunto Tejano
Accordion-Gypsy Jazz
Accordion-Irish
Accordion-Polish Polka
Accordion-Québécois
Afghan music and dance
African - Central African
African - country not specified
African - Ghana
African - Senegalese
African American Dance - Steppers
African American String Band
African dance
African Jazz Ensemble
African Music
African-American - Georgia Sea Islands
African-American - Hambone
African-American Children's Games
African-American Gospel Brass Band
African-American Gospel Choir
African-American Quilter
African-American Railroad Worksong
African-American Ring-Shout
African-American Sea Chanteys
Afro-American String Band
Afro-Brazilian
Afro-Cuban
Afro-Cuban bembe
Afro-Cuban Drumming
Alaskan regalia maker
Alkaline-glazed stoneware pottery
American Country Painting
American Folk Music
American Indian - Lakota Sioux Flute
American Indian - Ojibwe Storyteller
American Indian/European fiddle & dance
American Indian: Dakota Sioux
American Lumberjacks
American Piano Masters
American Popular Music
Andean
Anglo Stoneware Potter
Anglo-American Quilter
Anglo-American String Band Music
Anglo-American Whittler
Animal Imitations
Apache Basketweaver
Apache fiddle maker
Appalachian Ballads
Appalachian banjo
Appalachian Fiddle
Appalachian Guitar
Appalachian Music
Appalachian Musician
Appalachian Old Time Banjo
Appalachian singer-songwriter
Appalachian Songs & Ballads
Appalachian-Fiddle
Appalacian Program
Arabic Music
Armenian
Artful Juggling, music, and more
Auctioneering
Audience Sounds
Austrian
Autoharp
Bahamian Junkanoo Parade Band
Balinese Dance
Balladry
Balladry - Appalachian
Ballads
Banjo - 2-finger style
Banjo - 3-finger style
Banjo - Appalachian Style
Banjo - bare 3-finger style
Banjo - classical style
Banjo - flat-picked
Banjo - frailing style
Banjo - Melodic or Fiddle Style
Banjo - New Directions
Banjo - stroke style
banjo - various styles
Banjo tunes & songs
Banjo: 2-finger style
Banjo: clawhammer-style
Banjo-bluegrass
Banjo-Charlie Poole style
Banjo-Crucian "Scratch"
Banjo-Irish
Banjo-minstrel
Banjo-New Orleans Jazz
Barbershop Quartet
Basque
Bengali folk music
Bharata Natyam
Bird imitations
Black gospel on lap steel guitar
Black String Band
Black Stringband Violin
Blacksmith from Chamorra
Blue Ridge Piano Style
Bluegrass
Bluegrass - Banjo
Bluegrass - Fiddle
Bluegrass - Guitar
Bluegrass & Country Music
Bluegrass Gospel
Bluegrass/Old-Time
Bluegrass-mandolin
Blues
Blues - Boogie
Blues - Country
Blues - Delta
Blues - Detroit
Blues - Electric
Blues - Mississippi Delta
Blues - Piedmont
Blues - Texas Blues
Blues - Tidewater
Blues - Violin
Blues and R & B
Blues piano player & singer
Blues-Piano
Bobbin Lacemaker - German-American
Bomba y plena, salsa
Bones
Boogie Woogie Piano
Brass Band
Brass Quintet
Brazilian Capoeira
Brazilian Forró
Brazilian Music
Brazilian Percussion Ensemble
Brother-style Country duet
Buck and Tap Dance
Buck Dance
Bukharan Jewish Music
Bulgarian
Bulgarian Wedding Music
Button Box Music
Cajun
Cajun Gypsy Swing
Cajun Zydeco
Calentana mexicana
Calypso
Cambodian
Cambodian - Dance and Music
Cambodian - traditional Khmer
Cambodian Classical Dance
Cambodian Court Dancer / Coreographer
Cambodian Folk Dance & Music
Cambodian musician & teacher
Cambodian Silk Weaver
Cambodian Traditional Music
Canada-Ballad Traditions
Canadian Dance
Canary Island Singer
Candy Maker
Cape Breton
Cape Breton Music and Dance
Cape Breton song, music and dance
Cape Verdean Funana
Cape Verdean Morna
Cape Verdean Music
Caribbean Steel Pan
Caribbean-Dominican Merengue
Carnival maskmaker - Puerto Rico
Ceilidh Dance
Celtic
Central Asian Throat Singing
Cherokee Storyteller, Musician, and Dancer
Cherokee Tales
Chiapanecan Marimba
Chicano Singer, Musician, & Composer
Children's music with guitar
Chinese Classical Music
Chinese dulcimer (yang qin)
Chinese Dulcimer Ensemble
Chinese guzheng performer
Chinese Hammered Dulcimer
Chinese Lion Dance
Chinese Music
Chinese Opera
Chinese Pipa
Chinese Rod Puppetry
Chinese Zither & Hammered Dulcimer
Chinese zither and hammer dulcimer musician
Chinese-Erhu (strings)
Choral Singing
Classic Blues
Classic Tab Dancing
Classical Banjo
Classical Folk Dances of India
Clawhammer Banjo
Clog Dancing
Clown
Coiled Basketry
Colombian Harp
Colombian Vallenato
Columbian Dance Music
Comanche Flute
Community Band
Congolese Drumming & Dance
Congolese rumba
Congolese soukous
Conjunto
Conjunto Norteño
Contra Dance
Cook - Moroccan
Cook-French
Cook-Native American
Cook-Puerton Rican
Cook-Vietnamese
Corona Maker, Mexican-American
Country
Country - Classic
Country - Honky Tonk
Country & Western
Country Duet Singing -Brother Style
Country Gospel
Country Singing
Country, folk, bluegrass
Cowboy
Cowboy Poet
Craft- ukulele builder
Craft-banjo builder
Craft-Bobbin Lace "Mundillo"
Craft-classical guitar builder
Craft-Diving Helmet Maker
Craft-fiddle maker
Craft-hammock weaver
Craft-hardanger fiddle maker
Craft-harp builder
Craft-mandolin builder
Craft-Navajo Weaver
Craft-Paper Cutting Artist & Altarista
Craft-Passamaquoddy Basketry
Craft-Penobscot Root Club
Crafts - Armenian lacemaker
Crafts - basketmaking
Crafts - Laotian weaver
Crafts - Lithuanian weaver
Crafts - Lowell textile worker
Crafts - netmaking
Crafts - Woodcarving
Crafts-Acadian rug making, knitting, weaving
Craft-Salish Beadwork & Tanning
Crafts-Decorative Building Craftsman
Crafts-instrument building
Crafts-Orthodox Byzantine icon Woodcarving
Crafts-snowshoe making
Crafts-weaver
Craft-Traditional Drums
Craft-weaver, singer, storyteller
Creole & Zydeco
Creole and Cajun a capella singing
Croatian
Croatian Dance
Crucian
Crucian "Scratch"
Crucian Music
Crucian singer - Virgin Islands
Cuatro Maker
Cuban Soneros
Czech puppeteer
Czech Puppetry
Czech-American Bobbin Lace Maker
Czechoslovakian Dance
Dabke (also debke, dabka, dabkeh)
Dance - Flatfoot
Dance - Native American
Dance - Square and Contra
Dance - Tap
Dance from Hawaii & South India
Dance Instructor
Dance-appalachian
Dance-Carolinian Stick Dance
Dance-Hip Hop
Dance-Latin
Dance-Lindy Hop
Dances of South Asia
Dance-various
Decoy Carver
Dixieland Jazz
Dobro guitar
Dominican merengue
doo-wop
Dulcimer-Various Styles
Dutch Hop
East Indian Folk Dance
East Indian Music And Dance
Eastern European Folk Songs
Eastern European Music
English and Scottish Songs and Ballads
English ballads and sea shanties
English Folk Dance
English Songs and Ballads
Ethiopian
Ethiopian krar music
Ethiopian Spiritual Music
European Folk Music
Fiddle - Missouri
Fiddle - Shenandoah Style
"Fiddle - Various Styles
Fiddle - Various Styles"
Fiddle - Western Canadian
Fiddle - Western Longbow
Fiddle-Acadian
Fiddle-Armenian
Fiddle-Bluegrass
Fiddle-Cajun
Fiddle-Cape Breton
Fiddle-Creole & Zydeco
Fiddle-Eastern European
Fiddle-Franco-American
Fiddle-Franco-Canadian
Fiddle-Gypsy Jazz
Fiddle-Irish
Fiddle-Jazz
Fiddle-Klezmer
Fiddle-Mariachi
Fiddle-Old Time
Fiddle-Québécois
Fiddle-Scottish
Fiddle-Western Swing
Fife and Drum
Filipino Music and Dance
Finnish Accordion
Finnish Folk Dance
Finnish Folk Music
Finnish Harmonica
Finnish kantele (lap harp) player
Fisher Poet
Flamenco song, music & dance
Flute-Irish
Flying Indian Pole Dance
Folk & Traditional Music
Folk Violin
Folklorist, advocate, and presenter
Franco-American
Franco-American songs
Franco-American step dance
Franco-Canadian step dance
Franco-Canadian: Acadian
Franco-Canadian: Fiddle
Franco-Canadian: French Canadian
French
French - Acadian
French - traditional folk music
French traditional music
French-Canadian Music
French-Canadian Stepdance
Gambian
Gamelan Mitra Kusuma
Games - Children's
Garifuna - Belize coastal drumming and dancing
Georgia Sea Island Singers
German-American concertina maker
German-Russian
German-Russian Dutch Hop Music
Ghanaian Palmwine Guitar Music
Go Go Music - Junk Funk
Go Go Music - Junkyard Music
Go-Go Music
Gospel
Gospel - Shape Note Singing - Native American
Gospel - African American
Gospel - African-American a cappella Gospel
Gospel - Appalachian
Gospel - Brass Band
Gospel - Detroit
Gospel - Jubilee
Gospel - Various Styles
Gospel Brass Band
Gospel -Shape Note Singing
Gospel Steel Guitar
Gospel Various Styles
Gospel, rhythm & blues singer
gourd
Great Britain - folk music
Greek
Greek - Pontiaki and Rebetica Music
Greek - Pontic
Greek - Traditional Music
Greek Rembetica
Greek Smyrneika
Guatemalan-Marimba
Guinean Dancer, Musician & Composer
Guitar - Cajun
Guitar - Flatpicking
Guitar - Irish
Guitar - Lap Steel
Guitar - Resophonic
Guitar - Thumb Style
Guitar - Travis-style
Guitar - US
guitar various styles
Guitar-Bluegrass
Guitar-Blues
Guitar-Country
Guitar-finger picking
Guitar-gospel
Guitar-Gypsy Jazz
Guitar-Sacred Steel
Guitar-Western Swing
Gujarati Music And Dance
Gypsy Jazz
Haida (Native Alaskan) weaver
Haiku Poet & Historian
Haitian
Haitian misik rasin
Haitian rara
Haitian Twobadou
Harmonica
Harp
Hawaiian
Hawaiian - song
Hawaiian - Traditional
Hawaiian Chanter
Hawaiian Hula - dance and music
Hawaiian Lei Maker
Hawaiian Musician, Composer & Filmmaker
Hawaiian quiltmaking
Hawaiian Singers
Hawaiian-Slack-key guitar
Hip-Hop
Hispanic Music
Hispanic weaver
Hispanic-American Rawhide Worker
Hmong
Hmong weaver/embroiderer
Hollering
Honky-tonk Country
Hooked Rug Design
Humor
Humorist
Hungarian Gypsy
Indian
Indian - Kalbelia Dance and Music
Indian Bamboo Flutes
Indian-Indian Dance Ensemble
Instrument Maker
Intermission
Interview
Inuit Throat Singing
Inupiaq Eskimo
Inupiat Doll Maker
Irish
Irish - Stepdance
Irish - Traditional
Irish stepdancing
Irish-American
Irish-ballad singer
Isleños of St. Bernard Parish
Italian
Italian - Southern Music and Dance
Italian Folk Music
Italian-American Songs
Ivorian Dance Troupe
Jack Tales
Jam Band
Jamaican ska
Japanese
Japanese Taiko
Japanese-American Dancer
Jarocho
Jazz
Jazz - Guitar
Jazz - Latin
jazz violin and tap dance
Jazz-New Orleans Jazz Band
Jewish - Bukharan music and dance
Jewish - Cantor
Jewish - Klezmer
Jewish - Storytelling
Jewish Folk Music
Jews Harp
Juggling
Juglarias
Kashia Pomo Basket Maker
Kathak
Keyboard Artist
Khmer Wedding Ensemble
Kiowa & Comanche Traditions
Kiowa And Comanche Dancers
Kiowa regalia maker
Kiowa sacred song leader
Klezmer
Klezmer music
Klezmer-Moldavian
Korean
Korean dance, drumming, & music
Kuchipudi Classical Dance
Kumu Hula (hula master)
la musica tejana
la musica tejana, Michigan-style
Labor Songs
Lace Maker
Lakota - hoop dancer
Lakota flute music and hoop dancing
Lakota hoop dancer
Laotian - Vocal
Laotian Classical Music
Laotian Music and Dance
Latin American - Dueto Style
Latin Dance & Jazz
Latin/Caribbean
Lithuanian
Macedonian Music and Dance
Maine Country Music
Maine French Fiddle Players
Malian Music
mandolin
Mandolin Orchestra
Mardi Gras - African tradition
Mardi Gras chief/costume maker
Mardi Gras Indian
Mariachi
Marimba
Marricha
Merengue Tipico
Mexican
Mexican - Conjunto
Mexican - Jarocho from Veracruz
Mexican - Marimba
Mexican - Musica de Nuevo Mexico
Mexican - Tejano
Mexican Dance
Mexican folk music
Mexican Jarocho Music
Mexican String Band Music
Mexican-American Singer/Guitarist/Composer
Mexico - Michoacan
Mexico - Michoacan harpist
Michigan Heritage Award Winner 2000
Michigan Hungarian Roma
Middle Eastern Music
Mime & dance
Mississippi Delta Blues
Missouri-French Fiddler
Mountain Dulcimer
Mouth bow
Mouth music
Music and Dance of the Andes
Music, songs & stories from Maine & the Maritimes
Musica De Los Viejitos
Musica de Nuevo Mexico
Native American
Native American - Cherokee
Native American - Craftsman
Native American - Creek/Seminole
Native American - Hocak (Winnebago)
Native American - Iroquois
Native American - Laguna
Native American - Lakota
Native American - Mohawk
Native American - Muscogee (Creek) Nation of Okla.
Native American - Native Californian Song and Danc
Native American - Navajo
Native American - Penobscot
Native American - Seneca-Comanche
Native American - Tigua
Native American - Tohono O'odham
Native American - Walla Walla (Warm Springs)
Native American - Yup'ik
Native American - Zuni
Native American Choir
Native American Corn Husk Weaver
Native American drum and dance
Native American Drum Circle
Native American linguist & storyteller
Native American Music
Native American quillwork
Native American Storyteller
Native American -Yakima
Native American-Akwesasne Mohawk Nation
Native American-Cherokee
Native American-Cherokee/Choctaw
Native American-Choctaw
Native American-Intertribal
Native American-Nez Perce
Native American-Passamaquoddy
Native American-Seminole
Native American-Shoshone Regalia Maker
Near Eastern and Middle Eastern - Armenian
Near Eastern-Afghanistan
need
Nepalese Music
New England Fiddle Music
New England Folk Music
New England Verse
New Mexico folk music
New Orleans Brass Band
New Orleans Brass Bands and Mardi Gras - Dixieland
New Orleans Jazz
New Orleans Mardi Gras Indians
New Orleans Parade Band
New Orleans piano professor
New Orleans Rhythm & Blues
New Orleans Street Band and Dixieland